Aqib Hussain

Islāmābād, Pakistan

agibhussain2001@gmail.com

03331934975

linkedin.com/in/muhammadaqibhussainofficial

Summary

With over 8 years of experience in web development, starting from Blogger and progressing to custom development using HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, NodeJS, NuxtJS, and other frameworks, I have gained a deep understanding of various web development technologies. Despite my experience, I consider myself a beginner, always eager to learn new techniques and skills. As a BSCS student in my 6th semester at the Institute of Space Technology, I am looking for an entry-level position to further expand my knowledge and skills in the industry.

Experience

Developer

Wybe Network Aug 2018 - Present (5 years 7 months)

Web Developer

FixLife Oct 2022 - Nov 2022 (2 months)

Education



Institute of Space Technology (IST)

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science Aug 2020 - Aug 2024

Pak-Turk Maarif International Schools and Colleges

Intermediate, Computer Science Aug 2018 - Aug 2020

Muslim Hands School of Excellence

Matriculation, Computer Science Aug 2016 - Aug 2018



Course, Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User Feb 2023 - Mar 2023

Licenses & Certifications



Operating Systems and You: Becoming a Power User - Coursera

B32ZDELUMZJU

Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Computer Science • HTML5 • Bootstrap • Plesk • cPanel • WHMCS • WordPress • Nuxt.js • Node.js